sqwiggle.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy | Sqwiggle

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Sqwiggle collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Sqwiggle's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Sqwiggle's visitors use its website and applications. From time to time, Sqwiggle may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

Sqwiggle also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Sqwiggle does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Sqwiggle's websites choose to interact with Sqwiggle in ways that require Sqwiggle to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Sqwiggle gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Sqwiggle collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Sqwiggle. 

Sqwiggle does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Aggregated Statistics

Sqwiggle may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Sqwiggle may reveal how many downloads a particular version got, or say which features are most popular. However, Sqwiggle does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Sqwiggle discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Sqwiggle's behalf or to provide services available at Sqwiggle's websites or applications, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Sqwiggle's websites or applications, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Sqwiggle will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, Sqwiggle discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Sqwiggle believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Sqwiggle, third parties, or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Sqwiggle website or application and have supplied your email address, Sqwiggle may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Sqwiggle and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Sqwiggle takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Sqwiggle uses cookies to help Sqwiggle identify and track visitors, their usage of Sqwiggle website, and their website access preferences. Sqwiggle visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Sqwiggle's websites, with the drawback that account login and other certain features of Sqwiggle's websites will not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Sqwiggle may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Sqwiggle's sole discretion. Sqwiggle encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

Any questions about this policy can be sent to [howdy@sqwiggle.com](mailto:howdy@sqwiggle.com)
